Are you ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
KIDS:
Aye, aye, Captain.
儿童：
是的，是的，船长。
I can't hear you.
我听不到你说话。
Aye, aye, Captain!
是啊是啊，队长！
♪ Ooh!
♪ 哦！
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants!♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！♪
♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants!♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！♪
♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
♪ 如果是航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants!♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！♪
♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants!♪Ready?
♪ 海绵宝宝！♪ 准备好了吗？
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants!
♪ 海绵宝宝！
[ hearty laughter]
[爽朗的笑声]
[ piccolo playing]
[短笛演奏]
[ ocean waves lapping,
seagulls crying]
[海浪拍打着，
海鸥在哭泣]
So, I was all ready
to drain the fries,
所以，我已经准备好了
沥干薯条，
but I cooked the fries
slightly too long. So...
但我煮了薯条
有点太长了。所以...
SpongeBob...So here's where the
bizarre twist comes in.
海绵宝宝...所以这就是
奇怪的转折出现了。
SpongeBob...They weren't overcooked
at all!
海绵宝宝...他们没有煮过头
根本！
SpongeBob! Look!
海绵宝宝！看！
SPONGEBOB:
Wow!
海绵宝宝：
哇！
What happened to
the Krusty Krab?
发生了什么事
蟹堡王？
MR. KRABS:
Good morning!
先生。螃蟹：
早上好！
The Krusty Towers
is now open for business.
库斯蒂塔
现已开始营业。
Why did you build a hotel,
Mr. Krabs?
为什么要建酒店，
蟹老板？
I'm glad
you asked, son.
我很高兴
你问了，儿子。
Remember when I went to
that fast food convention
记得我去的时候
那个快餐大会
and stayed in
that fancy hotel?
并留在
那个豪华酒店？
I had a beautiful room.
我有一个漂亮的房间。
The employees were so friendly.
员工们非常友好。
They catered to me every whim,
他们满足了我的每一个突发奇想
no matter how demeaning it was,
不管它是多么有辱人格，
because they lived by a code.
因为他们遵循一套准则。
And that code was engraved
in fine gold
那段代码被刻在了
纯金
above the grand fireplace.
大壁炉上方。
Everything was perfect.
一切都很完美。
Until I got the bill!
直到我收到账单！
They charged me for everything.
他们向我收取一切费用。
$25.00 for a hamburger.
汉堡包 25 美元。
[ horn toots]
[喇叭嘟嘟]
If they could charge
that much for
a lousy burger,
如果他们可以充电
就这么多
一个糟糕的汉堡，
imagine how much
I could charge for
a lousy Krabby Patty.
想象一下有多少
我可以收费
一个糟糕的克拉比帕蒂。
And thus,
因此，
the Krusty Towers
was born.
库斯蒂塔
诞生了。
Why would anyone stay at a hotel
in Bikini Bottom?
为什么有人要住酒店
在比基尼底部？
It's in the middle
of scenic nowhere.
它在中间
风景无处。
There's nothing to do
but get stung by jellyfish.
无事可做
但被水母蜇了。
[ groaning]
[呻吟]
See?Eww.
看到了吗？呃。
Come inside.
进来吧。
Isn't it beautiful?
是不是很漂亮？
Where are all the new
hotel employees?
所有新的都在哪里
酒店员工？
Me first hotel guest.
我是第一个酒店客人。
Watch me reel him in.
看我把他卷进去。
Welcome to
the Krusty Towers,
欢迎来到
库斯蒂塔，
where our motto is,
我们的座右铭是，
"We shall never deny a guest
“我们永远不会拒绝客人
even the most ridiculous
request."
即使是最可笑的
请求。”
Oh, that's great.
哦，那太好了。
I'd like a double Krabby Patty
我想要一份双层蟹肉饼
with no onions
and extra pickles.
没有洋葱
和额外的泡菜。
If you want
a Krabby Patty,
如果你想要
蟹肉饼，
you have to rent a room,
and order room service.
你必须租一个房间，
并订购客房服务。
Ooh, I've only got
an hour for lunch.
哦，我只有
一个小时的午餐。
Boy, you reeled
that one in like a pro.
男孩，你晕倒了
那个就像专业人士一样。
Okay, Squidward,
好吧，章鱼哥，
you run
the front desk.
你跑
前台。
I'd like
a Krabby Patty, please.
我想要
请来一份蟹肉饼。
This is a hotel now.
这里现在是一家酒店。
If you want
a Krabby Patty,
如果你想要
蟹肉饼，
you'll have to get
a room, and order
room service.
你必须得到
一个房间，并订购
客房服务。
Okay.
One Krabby Patty and one room.
好的。
一份蟹肉饼和一间房间。
With cheese.
配奶酪。
Oh, and can I get cheese
on the Krabby Patty, too?
哦，我可以买奶酪吗
也吃蟹黄饼吗？
Patrick,
帕特里克，
you only live
400 yards away.
你只活着
400 码外。
Why do you want
to check into a hotel?
你为什么想要
入住酒店？
Sometimes I just need to get
away from it all.
有时我只需要得到
远离这一切。
Wow, this hotel
has everything.
哇这个酒店
拥有一切。
Give me that.
给我那个。
Now sign
the register.
现在签名
寄存器。
I didn't know
there would be a test.
我不知道
将会有一个测试。
I didn't study!
我没学过！
Patrick, all you have
to do is write your name.
帕特里克，你拥有的一切
要做的就是写下你的名字。
Oh, okay.
哦好的。
Do you mind?
你介意吗？
Don't look.
别看。
Um...
嗯...
Done.
完毕。
Close enough.
足够接近。
Here's your
room key.
这是你的
房间钥匙。
I'll need some help
with my bags.
我需要一些帮助
带着我的包。
How can you
have bags?
你怎么可以
有包吗？
You just found out
this is a hotel.
你刚刚发现
这是一家酒店。
This is a hotel?
这是酒店？
D-oh!
SpongeBob?
噢！
海绵宝宝？
Yes, Squidward.
是的，章鱼哥。
Take Patrick and his bags
to his room.
带上帕特里克和他的包
到他的房间。
What about my Krabby Patty?
我的蟹黄饼呢？
And bring him a Krabby Patty.
给他带一份蟹肉饼。
Squidward, you can take
Patrick's bags up to his room.
章鱼哥，你可以带
帕特里克把行李搬到他的房间。
SpongeBob, you go make
the Krabby Patty.
海绵宝宝，你去创造吧
蟹肉饼。
Oh, Mr. Krabs.
哦，蟹老板。
What's the matter?
怎么了？
Afraid of a little
manual labor?
害怕一点点
体力劳动？
"I'm Squidward, and I have
to work for a living."
“我是章鱼哥，我有
为了谋生而工作。”
Boo-hoo-hoo.
呜呼呼。
Fine.
美好的。
Let's go,
Patrick.
我们走吧，
帕特里克.
[ groaning]
[呻吟]
This elevator is
for guests only.
这台电梯是
仅供客人使用。
Take the employee
elevator.
拿员工来说
电梯。
[ squeaking]
[吱吱声]
[ bell rings]
[铃声响起]
[ angry muttering]
[愤怒的嘀咕]
[ bell rings]
[铃声响起]
What's in
these bags? Rocks?
里面有什么
这些袋子？岩石？
Hey, these are rocks!
嘿，这些是石头！
Why is your suitcase
full of rocks?
为什么你的行李箱
充满了岩石？
I don't tell you
how to live your life!
我不告诉你
如何过你的生活！
Well, here's your room.
嗯，这是你的房间。
Wow.
哇。
Enjoy your stay.
祝您住宿愉快。
Squidward, wait.
章鱼哥，等等。
Keep up the good work,
继续做好工作，
and there will be more
where that came from.
并且还会有更多
那是从哪里来的。
Your Krabby Patty, sir.
你的蟹肉饼，先生。
Hey, Squidward,
cool rock.
嘿，章鱼哥，
很酷的摇滚。
Hold on a second,
SpongeBob.
等一下，
海绵宝宝。
Here you are,
my good man.
你在这里，
我的好人。
Thank you, Patrick.
谢谢你，帕特里克。
There's plenty more where that
came from, my good friend.
还有很多地方
来自，我的好朋友。
[ grumbling]
[抱怨]
Squidward!What now?
章鱼哥！现在怎么办？
I don't like crusts
on my sandwich.
我不喜欢面包皮
在我的三明治上。
It's a bun.
这是一个馒头。
It's all crust.
都是地壳。
How am I supposed to cut
the crust off a bun?
我该怎么剪
面包皮掉下来了吗？
Peel it.
剥皮。
Happy?Yay!
快乐吗？耶！
SPONGEBOB:
Room service.
海绵宝宝：
客房服务。
Here's the 50 Krabby Patties
you ordered.
这是 50 个蟹黄肉饼
你订购了。
Could you do
one more thing for me?
你能做吗
对我来说还有一件事吗？
Why don't you ask
SpongeBob?
你为什么不问
海绵宝宝？
Good idea,
Squidward.
好主意，
章鱼哥。
How may I serve you, sir?
先生，我该如何为您服务？
I need you to eat these
Krabby Patties with me.
我需要你吃这些
蟹肉饼和我一起。
Oh, yes, sir.
哦，是的，先生。
[ bell rings]
[铃声响起]
Uh-huh.
Hold on.
嗯嗯。
坚持，稍等。
Squidward! Patrick
needs your help.
章鱼哥！帕特里克
需要你的帮助。
What?!
Why didn't he ask me
什么？！
他为什么不问我
before I walked all the way
downstairs?
在我走完全程之前
楼下？
He said he didn't
want to bother you.
他说他没有
想打扰你。
But he got over it.
但他克服了。
Hooray!
万岁！
Thanks, Squidward.
谢谢，章鱼哥。
[ toilet flushes]
[马桶冲水]
Mr. Krabs,
this is ridiculous.
蟹老板先生，
这太荒谬了。
Patrick's being completely
unreasonable.
帕特里克完全是
不合理。
He can be as unreasonable
as he wants.
他也可以如此不讲道理
如他所愿。
The plaque, Squidward!
The plaque!
牌匾，章鱼哥！
牌匾！
But Mr. Krabs...
但是蟹老板...
Deny no guest!
不谢客！
[ phone rings]
[电话响]
Well, hello, Patrick.
嗯，你好，帕特里克。
You need Squidward
to come up right away?
你需要章鱼哥
马上上来吗？
He'll be
right there.
他会是
就在那里。
A bubble bath?
泡泡浴？
Why would I give you
a bubble bath?
我为什么要给你
泡泡浴？
Well, because Mr. Krabs
said you would.
嗯，因为蟹老板
你说你会的。
Be sure to make my back
extra shiny clean.
一定要让我回来
格外闪亮干净。
That's it!
就是这样！
I've had enough!
我已经受够了！
Squidward, wait!
章鱼哥，等等！
The toilet's backed up again!
厕所又堵了！
Hey, hey, you can't
take that elevator.
嘿嘿嘿你不能
乘那个电梯。
You're an employee.
你是一名员工。
Not anymore.
不再。
I quit.
我不干了。
Quit?
辞职？
You can't quit.
你不能放弃。
Welcome to
the Krusty Towers.
欢迎来到
库斯蒂塔。
Squidward?!
章鱼哥？！
One room, please,
on the top floor.
请一间房，
在顶楼。
What do you think
you're doing?
你觉得怎么样
你在做什么？
I need a vacation.
我需要一个假期。
I'm overworked.
我劳累过度了。
And what better place to relax
than Krusty Towers,
还有什么更好的放松场所
比库斯蒂塔，
where we shall never deny
a guest
我们永远不会否认
一位客人
even the most ridiculous
request.
即使是最可笑的
请求。
I don't have to rent you a room.
我不必给你租房间。
I got cash.
我有现金。
D-oh...
Here's your room key.
噢……
这是你的房间钥匙。
SpongeBob, carry my things
to my room.
海绵宝宝，帮我搬东西
到我的房间。
Aye, aye, guest sir.
是啊是啊，客人先生。
[ crashes]
[崩溃]
And you can carry me
to my room.
你可以载着我
到我的房间。
And why in tarnation
would I do that?
为什么在塔尼翁中
我会那样做吗？
You've got four legs
that aren't broken.
你有四条腿
没有损坏。
The plaque.
牌匾。
Too bad we couldn't take
the elevator,
可惜我们不能接受
电梯，
but it is for guests only,
and you are an employee.
但仅供客人使用，
而你是一名员工。
Your room, sir.
你的房间，先生。
And I'd like to order
room service.
我想订购
客房服务。
I'd like a Krabby Patty
with cheese, toenail clippings
我想要一份蟹肉饼
配奶酪、脚趾甲屑
and nose hairs.
和鼻毛。
[ squeals]
[尖叫声]
You've got to be kidding me!
你一定是在开玩笑吧！
And I want it here
in five seconds.
我想要它在这里
五秒钟后。
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
Here you are, sir.
在这里，先生。
Well, you got
your stinky sandwich.
好吧，你得到了
你的臭三明治。
Now eat it.
现在吃吧。
Oh, I'm not going
to eat this.
哦，我不去
吃这个。
You are.
你是。
What?!
什么？！
You're out of your mind if you
think I'm going to eat that.
如果你疯了，你就疯了
我想我要吃那个。
Psst, that's not really
a Krabby Patty
嘘，那不是真的
蟹肉饼
with cheese, toenails
and nose hair.
配奶酪、脚趾甲
和鼻毛。
[ chuckles]:
Now I get you, boy.
[轻笑]：
现在我明白你了，孩子。
All right, Squidward.
好吧，章鱼哥。
[ laughter]
[笑声]
SpongeBob!Sorry, Mr. Krabs.
海绵宝宝！对不起，蟹老板。
We were all out
of cheese.
我们都出去了
奶酪。
Hooray!
万岁！
[ phone ringing]
[电话铃声]
What is it,
Squidward?
这是什么，
章鱼哥？
Send up a dozen cookies
just like mother used to make.
发送一打饼干
就像妈妈以前做的那样。
Here's your homemade cookies.
这是你自制的饼干。
These don't taste anything
like mom used to make.
这些没有什么味道
就像妈妈以前做的那样。
Well, how did your mother
make 'em?
嗯，你妈妈怎么样？
让他们？
How should I know?
我怎么知道？
Ask my mother.
问我妈妈。
[ doorbell rings]
[门铃响]
Hello.
你好。
[ gasps]
[喘气]
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
No good, Mr. Krabs.
不好，蟹老板。
Allow me, boys.
请允许我，孩子们。
Great.
伟大的。
Now that me laundry
is in the trunk...
现在我洗衣服
在后备箱里...
There's room for you
to sit up front.
有你的空间
坐在前面。
Let's go bake some cookies,
boys.
我们去烤一些饼干吧
男孩们。
Hooray!
万岁！
Well?
出色地？
I'm impressed.
我印象深刻。
These are just like mother
used to make.
这些就像妈妈一样
用来制作。
I just wish mom
was a better cook.
我只希望妈妈
是一个更好的厨师。
So you're all taken care of.
所以你们都被照顾了。
Just one teensy, tiny problem.
只是一个很小的问题。
This room is hideous.
这个房间很丑陋。
Redesign it.
重新设计它。
Neptune the 14th would be nice.
海王星14宫会很好。
What?
什么？
"We shall never deny
a guest
“我们永远不会否认
一位客人
even the most
ridiculous request."
甚至是最
可笑的要求。”
[ screaming]
[尖叫]
Perfect!
完美的！
This room is exactly
the same as when we started!
这个房间正是
和我们刚开始的时候一样！
Nothing like getting
back to the basics.
没有什么比得到
回到基础。
Let's get out of here,
SpongeBob.
我们离开这里吧
海绵宝宝。
Oh, before you leave,
哦，在你离开之前，
I want to go swimming.
我想去游泳。
The pool is out back.
泳池就在后面。
[ laughing]:
Are you crazy?
[笑]：
你疯了吗？
I'm not going outside to swim.
我不会去外面游泳。
Come on in.
进来吧。
The water's fine.
水还好啊
Anything else stupid
还有什么蠢事
and unreasonable
that you want?
和不合理的
你想要什么？
Nope, that's it.
不，就是这样。
You don't need me to chew
your food for you,
你不需要我咀嚼
你的食物给你，
or make you a back scratcher
out of my own spine?
或者让你挠背
出于我自己的脊椎？
Or maybe extinguish the sun
或者也许熄灭太阳
so the light
don't get in your eyes?
所以光
不要进入你的眼睛吗？
No, I'm good.
不，我很好。
Me, too.
我也是。
Wow!
哇！
An indoor pool.
一个室内游泳池。
This place is fancy!
这个地方很别致！
Cannonball!
炮弹！
[ laughing]
[笑]
[ loud crash]
[巨响]
MR. KRABS:
Oh!
先生。螃蟹：
哦！
That hotel was a bad idea
from the start.
那家酒店是个坏主意
从一开始。
That was a hotel?
那是一家酒店？
Your bill, sir.
你的账单，先生。
$15,000?
15,000 美元？
You're not going to have
a heart attack, are you?
你不会有
心脏病发作了，你是吗？
Not at these prices.
不是按照这些价格。
Forget hotels.
忘记酒店吧。
This hospital racket
is where the money is.
这家医院的球拍
就是钱所在。
This is a hospital?
这是医院？
Pack your bags, boys.
收拾好行李，孩子们。
You're going
to medical school.
你要去
到医学院。
Hooray!
万岁！
Oh, boy.
哦，男孩。
Good morning, Mrs. Puff.
I'm Mr. Fitz.
早上好，普芙夫人。
我是菲茨先生。
I represent the Voting Teachers
Accreditation Bureau.
我代表投票的老师
认证局。
As you know, your teaching
certificate is up for renewal.
如您所知，您的教学
证书即将更新。
However,
we've noticed there have been
然而，
我们注意到有
an unusually large amount
of failings from this classroom.
数额异常大
这间教室的失败。
That's impossible.
那是不可能的。
In all my years of teaching,
在我多年的教学生涯中，
only one student
has failed my class.
只有一名学生
我的课不及格。
Yes, but he's failed
1,258,056 times.
是的，但是他失败了
1,258,056 次。
SPONGEBOB:
Ai-ai-ai-ai-ai-ai!
海绵宝宝：
哎哎哎哎哎！
You don't understand.
你不明白。
SpongeBob is... unteachable.
海绵宝宝是……不可教的。
We cannotblame the students for
the incompetence of the teacher.
我们不能责怪学生
老师的无能。
SPONGEBOB:
Honk, honk!
Beep-beep!
海绵宝宝：
喇叭，喇叭！
嘟嘟！
I'm ready to drive!
我准备开车了！
[ horn honks]
[喇叭鸣响]
Are you ready for
my driving test
today, Mrs. Puff?
你准备好了吗
我的驾驶考试
今天，普芙女士？
Okay, Mrs. Puff,
if SpongeBob fails this test,
好吧，普芙女士，
如果海绵宝宝没有通过这个测试，
you will be replaced.
你将会被取代。
Okay, SpongeBob,
let's demonstrate for Mr. Fitz
好吧，海绵宝宝，
让我们为菲茨先生演示一下
everything I've taught you
in boating school.
我教给你的一切
在划船学校。
[ chuckles]:
Now,
[轻笑]：
现在，
what's the first thing we do
before we start boating?
我们做的第一件事是什么
在我们开始划船之前？
Oh! Seatbelt-a-rooni.
One second.
哦！安全带-a-rooni。
一秒钟。
[ grunting]
[咕噜声]
Then what do you do?
那你怎么办？
Start the engine?Yes.
启动发动机？是的。
[ engine starts]
[发动机启动]
What do I do now?Drive the boat.
我现在该怎么办？驾驶船。
Did I pass this
time, Mrs. Puff?
我通过了吗
时间到了吗，普夫夫人？
No, SpongeBob.
不，海绵宝宝。
You failed.
你失败了。
I failed?
我失败了？
It is not you that's
failed, SpongeBob.
那不是你
失败了，海绵宝宝。
It's Mrs. Puff
that's failed you.
这是泡芙夫人
那让你失败了。
You are relieved
of your teaching duties.
你放心了
你的教学职责。
I won't be teaching
SpongeBob anymore?
我不会教书
现在还有海绵宝宝吗？
[ laughing]
[笑]
[ laughing loudly]
[大声笑]
No more... SpongeBob?
不再...海绵宝宝？
I thought this day
would never come.
我以为这一天
永远不会来。
[ continues laughing]
[继续笑]
Whoo-hoo!
呼呼！
Good-bye, SpongeBob!
再见，海绵宝宝！
Have a nice life.
祝你生活愉快。
Free at last!
终于自由了！
SPONGEBOB:
I got Mrs. Puff fired.
海绵宝宝：
我把普夫太太解雇了。
[ booming footsteps]
[轰隆隆的脚步声]
Hello, worthless students.
你好，无用的学生。
I'm your new instructor.
我是你们的新教练。
No one's ever failed my class
我的课从来没有人不及格
that's lived through it.
那是经历过的。
I can assure you,
these next four weeks
我可以向你保证，
接下来的四个星期
will be the worst years
of your miserable lives.
将是最糟糕的几年
你悲惨的生活。
Your spines will break.
你的脊椎会折断。
Your teeth will ache.
你的牙齿会痛。
Your eyes will be bloodshot.
你的眼睛会布满血丝。
[ students whimpering]
[学生抽泣]
You will drive
out of this school in style,
你会开车
以时尚的方式走出这所学校，
or you will be carted out
否则你会被赶出去
in your granny's
handbasket.
在你奶奶家
手提篮。
Everyone will follow
the rules of the class.
大家都会跟着
班级规则。
First rule: no talking.
第一条规则：不许说话。
Does that mean...
这是不是意味着...
Second rule:
no eating in my class.
第二条规则：
我的课上不许吃东西。
Would anyone care for a bon-bon?
有人会喜欢糖果吗？
Uh, I'll eat one.
呃，我就吃一个。
[ students gasp]
[学生喘气]
Pick your favorite.
选择你最喜欢的。
How's it taste?
味道怎么样？
It's a delightful
taste sensation.
这是一个令人愉快的
味觉感觉。
No eating in my classroom!
不准在我的教室里吃东西！
Now, if anyone else
is man enough
现在，如果还有其他人
够男人吗
to stay in this class...
留在这个班级...
Looks like you're
the man... Sponge.
看来你是
这个男人……海绵。
I am?
我是？
Do you want to learn
how to drive or what?Yes, sir!
你想学吗
如何开车还是什么？是的，先生！
I'm ready to drive!
我准备开车了！
What do you think
you're doing?
你觉得怎么样
你在做什么？
Ready for my test, sir.You're not ready
准备好接受我的测试了，先生。你还没准备好
to drive yet-- until
you learn thatfirst.
还可以开车——直到
你先学那个。
This is the most grueling
driving course ever devised.
这是最累人的
曾经设计过的驾驶课程。
You will learn every turn,
bump and crack on it.
每一个回合你都会学到，
其上有碰撞和裂纹。
You'll start out
crawling it.
你将开始
爬行它。
Crawl?
爬行？
Hup two, hup two,
hup two, hup two!
哈二哈哈二，
哈二哈，哈哈二！
Left turn!
左转！
Crack! Bump! Nickel!
裂缝！撞！镍！
Hey, a nickel!
嘿，五分钱！
Keep your eyes on the road,
cadet![ gasps]
眼睛要一直盯着路，
学员！[喘气]
SPONGEBOB:
Pebble!
海绵宝宝：
卵石！
Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa
whoa-whoa-whoa!
哇-哇-哇-哇
哇-哇-哇！
Ow...!
哎呀……！
Wow...!
哇...！
[ screaming]
[尖叫]
Wow...!
哇...！
[ screaming]
[尖叫]
Wow...!
哇...！
Aah...!
啊啊……！
[ sighs]:
Whew!
[叹气]：
哇！
I'm ashamed
of you, cadet.
我很羞愧
你，学员。
Tripped up by a wee pebble.
被小石子绊倒了。
What are you supposed to
be learning in my class?
你应该做什么
在我的课堂上学习吗？
How to drive, sir?
先生，怎么开车？
Affirmative.
But before you learn to drive,
肯定。
但在你学会开车之前
you must learn
to crawl.
你必须学习
爬行。
And then you
learn to walk,
然后你
学会走路，
and then you
learn to run.
然后你
学会跑步。
But before you learn to walk,
you must learn to crawl!
但在你学会走路之前
你必须学会爬行！
I want you to crawl!
我要你爬行！
Sir, yes, sir!
先生，是的，先生！
Now, get out there!
现在，出去吧！
[ shoes screech]
[鞋子的尖叫声]
Hut! Hut!
小屋！小屋！
[ shoes screech]
[鞋子的尖叫声]
Every good boater needs to know
his vehicle inside and out.
每个优秀的划船者都需要知道
他的车里里外外。
Here. Go take
that boat apart.
这里。去拿
那艘船分开了。
I'm impressed, son.
我很感动，儿子。
Put it back together again!
再把它装回去！
[ chuckles]:
Oh, that'll be easy.
[轻笑]：
哦，那会很容易。
Are you sure?
你确定吗？
Um, yeah.
嗯，是的。
You just put the jing-a-mahoos
on the poo-hickey and, uh...
你只要把 jing-a-mahoos
在便便吻痕上，呃……
I might need
a couple of minutes.
我可能需要
几分钟。
[ snoring]It's ready, Sarge!
[打鼾]准备好了，中士！
Jumping jellyfish!
跳跃的水母！
[ bell dings]
[铃声]
Watch for pedestrians.
Check mirrors.
注意行人。
检查镜子。
Observe that speed limit.
遵守该速度限制。
Watch for pedestri... ans!
注意行人！
Whoa!
哇！
Aah! Whoa!
啊啊！哇！
Oh! Oh! Oh!
哦！哦！哦！
Wow! Oh! Oh!
哇！哦！哦！
So, um, how'd I do?
那么，嗯，我做得怎么样？
How'd you do?
你怎么样？
Why don't you ask
the shattered remains
你为什么不问
破碎的遗骸
of this pedestrian
这位行人的
how you did?!
你怎么样？！
Now I know this course forward,
backward and sideways.
现在我知道了前进的方向，
向后和侧向。
Am I ready to get
behind the wheel?
我准备好了吗
坐在方向盘后面？
Not quite.
不完全是。
Now do it blindfolded.
现在蒙着眼睛做。
[ horn honks, loud crash]
[喇叭鸣响，巨响]
1,003, 1,004, 1,005...
Oh, pebble number 143.
哦，143 号卵石。
Ha! You will not trip me up
again, pebble number 143.
哈!你不会绊倒我的
又是 143 号卵石。
1,006, 1,007, 1,008...
Old lady with
a ham sandwich.
老太太与
火腿三明治。
1,009,
1,010, 1,011,
1,012, one th...
1,012，分之一...
Congratulations.
恭喜。
You're ready to get
behind the wheel.
你已经准备好获得
方向盘后面。
Really? I'm ready!
真的吗？我准备好了！
I'm ready! I'm...
我准备好了！我是...
[ crash]
[ 碰撞]
Let's see what
I taught you, laddie.
让我们看看是什么
我教过你的，小伙子。
Yes, sir!
是的，先生！
Left turn at
pebble number 143.
左转于
143号卵石。
SPONGEBOB:
Kid with a ball.
Nice boy.
海绵宝宝：
有球的孩子。
好男孩。
Nice driving.
驾驶得很好。
Now parallel park up ahead.
现在在前面平行停车。
Very good.
非常好。
Now, boy, the time has come
to show Mr. Fitz
现在，孩子，时候到了
给菲茨先生看
what you learned.
Yes, sir!
你学到了什么。
是的，先生！
Step one: seat belts!
第一步：系好安全带！
Excellent work, cadet.
干得好，学员。
What's next?
接下来怎么办？
Step two would be:
ignite engine.
第二步是：
点燃发动机。
Step three.
第三步。
Step three would be:
第三步是：
engage blindfold!
蒙住眼睛！
What? You can't drive a boat
with a blindfold on.
什么？你不能驾驶船
带着眼罩。
That's illegal.
这是非法的。
But I can't do it
without a blindfold.
但我做不到
不蒙眼。
Drive, boy! Drive!
开车吧，小伙子！驾驶！
[ explosion]
[爆炸]
Mayday! Mayday!
劳动节！劳动节！
You're off course!
你偏离了轨道！
[ crashing, banging]
[碰撞、撞击]
[ rumbling]
[隆隆声]
[ screaming]
[尖叫]
Oh...
哦...
I feel so serene
now that I'm away
我感觉如此平静
现在我走了
from that homicidal maniac,
SpongeBob.
来自那个杀人狂，
海绵宝宝。
[ horn honks]
[喇叭鸣响]
The brake, son!
刹车，儿子！
Aye, aye, sir.
是啊，是啊，先生。
Here you go, sir--
all I had to do
给你，先生——
我必须做的一切
was unscrew
two little bolts.
被拧开
两个小螺栓。
I'm going to stop
this thing!
我要停下来
这东西！
Tell my wife I love her!
告诉我的妻子我爱她！
Come get some!
快来拿一些吧！
Man down! Man down!
人员受伤倒地！人员受伤倒地！
[ loud banging]Uh, sorry. Excuse me. Sorry.
[大声敲击]呃，抱歉。打扰一下。对不起。
Hey, SpongeBob.Sorry, Patrick, I can't stop
to talk right now.
嘿，海绵宝宝。对不起，帕特里克，我无法停止
现在就说话。
I can't see!
我看不见！
My pants!
我的裤子！
Hey! I can't see.
嘿！我看不到。
[ screams]
[尖叫声]
Did I pass?
我通过了吗？
Well, if there was
a "destroy the city"
好吧，如果有的话
一个“毁城”
part of the test,
you wouldhave.
测试的一部分，
你会的。
The nerve of
some people!
的神经
有些人！
Sorry, SpongeBob,
you failed again.
对不起，海绵宝宝，
你又失败了。
Even our finest instructor
could not teach you.
即使是我们最好的教练
无法教你。
Mrs. Puff, you're
hired again.
泡芙女士，你是
再次受聘。
Hey, Mrs. Puff.
嘿，帕夫夫人。
Sorry I'm "unteachable."
抱歉，我是“不可教的”。
It's okay.
没关系。
Mr. Fitz gave me
my teaching certificate back.
菲茨先生给了我
我的教师资格证回来了。
[ sniffles]:
And your dossier was destroyed
in the explosion.
[抽鼻子]：
你的档案被毁了
在爆炸中。
So it's as if
you never failed.
所以就好像
你从来没有失败过。
I got you a "welcome back" gift,
Mrs. Puff.
我给你准备了一份“欢迎回来”的礼物
泡芙女士。
I found all the pieces and
glued them back together.
我找到了所有的碎片并且
将它们重新粘在一起。
I promise it won't
take me a million
tries thistime.
我保证不会
拿我一百万
这次尝试一下。
[ sobbing]
[抽泣]
Captioning sponsored by
MTV NETWORKS
字幕赞助商
MTV 网络
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH 2 F1
标题为
WGBH 2 F1 媒体访问组